BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Audio and Visual Material, 1947-1968, undated; 5
  This is a mixed media collection containing audio tapes and phonographs of sermons, most given by White. It also includes photographs taken while White was affiliated with Baylor University as well as family photographs. There are three subseries: I. Recordings, II. Visual Material, and III. Photographs.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photo negative; Photographic print; Reel to reel tapes
  - Recordings, 1947-1968, undated; 1
    - Baylor Day Address, 1949 December 2 (Box 281, Folder 13)
    - Dr. White's Sermon: I Corintians at Paisano, 1963 July (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Campus Crusade for Christ presents “What Christians Believe”, undated (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - “Christian Responsibility in Education”, undated (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Dr. White’s Address for State Convention, undated (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Dr. White’s Sermon: First Baptist Church, Austin, 1947 August 3 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Dr. White’s Sermon: First Baptist Church, Dallas (1 of 2), 1968 Summer (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Dr. White’s Sermon: First Baptist Church, Dallas (2 of 2), 1968 Summer (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - “Evangelism and the University”, 1961 March 23 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Hall of Mirrors by Dr. White and Dr. W. C. Cook, 1965 September 5 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, 1948 April (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Visual Material, 1948, undated; 2
    - Banquet Honoring Dr. and Mrs. W. R. White scrapbook, 1948 January 22 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Engraving Plate with Prints, undated (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - William R. White framed photographs, undated (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1949, 1957, undated; 3
    - Baylor University Campus (1 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Baylor University Campus (2 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Baylor University Campus (3 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Boy Scouts, undated (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Catherine White (1 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Catherine White (2 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Catherine White (3 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - Edna White, undated (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Events at Baylor University, undated (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - General Photos (1 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - General Photos (2 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - General Photos (3 of 3), undated (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - Group Photos, undated (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - Meetings, undated (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - Negatives of photos from Sam Houston’s relatives honored at Baylor University, undated (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - Paisano Baptist Encampment, undated (Box 284, Folder 16)
    - Personal Meetings, undated (Box 284, Folder 17)
    - Photos from Archie Taylor, undated (Box 284, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, 1957 (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - President Dwight Eisenhower, 1957 (Box 284, Folder 20)
    - Public Relations Photos from Debbie Stewart, undated (Box 284, Folder 21)
    - Special Occasions, undated (Box 284, Folder 22)
    - White Family Photos, undated (Box 284, Folder 23)
    - White’s Speech for Southern Baptist Home Mission, 1949 (Box 284, Folder 24)
    - William R. White, undated (Box 284, Folder 25)
    - William R. White at a desk, undated (Box 284, Folder 26)
    - William R. White at Air Force Base, undated (Box 284, Folder 27)
    - William R. White at Commencements (1 of 2), undated (Box 284, Folder 28)
    - William R. White at Commencements (2 of 2), undated (Box 284, Folder 29)
    - William R. White at various activities, undated (Box 284, Folder 30)